Stereographic Cards
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Stereographic Cards, 2.1.8
  - Verso: Filipino Cascoes, or Freight Boats, on the River Front of Manila, P. I.: These curiously formed boats are of the type used throughout the, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 96-verso (Box 1609)
  - The Lovely Sea-girt Torii of Miyajima, Japan., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 97 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Gateway to the Shinto Temple of Miyajima, Japan: One of the most curious developments of architecture to be met with in the Orient, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 97-verso (Box 1609)
  - Girls Picking Tea on a Famous Plantation at Uji, among the Sunny Hills of old Japan., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 98 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Girls Picking Tea on Plantation at Uji, Japan: You are looking nearly north towards Kyoto, ten miles away beyond those hills covered with, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 98-verso (Box 1609)
  - A Family Picnic under the Cherry Blossoms, Omuro Gosho, Kyoto, Japan., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 99 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: A Family Picnic under the Cherry Blossoms, Omuro Gosho, Kyoto, Japan: In Japan the blossoming time of the cherry trees is the occasion, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 99-verso (Box 1609)
  - A Country Girl among the Famous Tea Fields of Shizuoka, Japan., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 100 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Among the Famous Tea Fields of Shizuoka, Japan: In Japan where the population is large in proportion ot the size of the country, it, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 100-verso (Box 1609)
  Box 1610
- Stereographic Cards, 2.1.8
  - New York Yankee Lou Gehrig, an Immortal of the Diamond, 1932 World Series., circa 1930s; 1 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: An Immortal of the Diamond Lou Gehrig: It is Lou Gehrig, first baseman for the New York Yankees since 1925, who smiles a greeting at you., circa 1930s; 1-verso (Box 1610)
  - Gene Sarazen, U. S. Open Champion, Receives Cup from President Ramsey, Fresh Meadow Course, Flushing, New York., circa 1930s; 2 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Gene Sarazen, the Golf Champion: It probably will be years before a golf championship provides as thrilling a climax as did the work of, circa 1930s; 2-verso (Box 1610)
  - Equestrian Sports Joe Aleshire, a Half-bred U. S. Government Horse, with Captain William Bradford in the Saddle, Jumping a Hurdle, Olympic Games, Los Angeles., circa 1930s; 3 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Equestrian Sports, 1932 Olympics: The magnificent polo fields of the Riviera Country Club in Los Angeles County, California, were the, circa 1930s; 3-verso (Box 1610)
  - Woodrow Wilson, 28th President of the United States., circa 1930s; 4 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Woodrow Wilson 28th President of the United States: Because of the split in the Republican party in 1912, the Democrats won the election, circa 1930s; 4-verso (Box 1610)
  - The Flying Major, James H. Doolittle (at left with arms folded), Who Linked the Three Capitals of Ottawa, Washington and Mexico City., circa 1930s; 5 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: The Flying Major, James H. Doolittle: The first airman to receive the degree of Doctor of Aeronautical Engineering from the Massachusetts, circa 1930s; 5-verso (Box 1610)
  - Gov. Franklin D. Roosevelt, the Presidential Nominee of the Democratic Party, at Chicago, Ill., circa 1930s; 6 (Box 1610)
  - [Stereoscopic image of Lowell Thomas], circa 1930s; 7 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Radio Announcer and Correspondent, circa 1930s; 7-verso (Box 1610)
  - [Stereoscopic image of Lowell Thomas], circa 1930s; 8 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Radio Announcer and Correspondent, circa 1930s; 8-verso (Box 1610)
  - [Stereoscopic image of Lowell Thomas with Prosecuting Attorney Johnston], circa 1930s; 9 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Radio Announcer and Correspondent with Prosecuting Attorney Johnston (the man who put Al Capone behind the bars)., circa 1930s; 9-verso (Box 1610)
  - Herbert Hoover., circa 1930s; 10 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Herbert Hoover, Servant of Humanity and President-Elect: Born at West Branch, Ia., Aug. 10, 1874. Elected President of the United States, circa 1930s; 10-verso (Box 1610)
  - Will Rogers, Humorist, Was in the Press Section for Both Conventions, Chicago., circa 1930s; 11 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Will Rogers, Humorist: Indispensable as a commentator on American life and events, what is the reason behind the former Oklahoma, circa 1930s; 11-verso (Box 1610)
  - Bobby Jones Playing Out of a Sand Trap to the Green, Winged Foot Country Club, Mamaroneck, N. Y. Note Ball in Air., circa 1930s; 12 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Bobby Jones Playing from a Bunker: Bobby Jones, in playing from a bunker, here gives a fine example of using his head as the anchor, circa 1930s; 12-verso (Box 1610)
  - Prime Minister of England Addressing Final Session of Naval Conference, London, England., circa 1930s; 13 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Final Session of the Naval Conference, St. James Palace, London: On April 22, 1930, delegates from the world's five leading naval powers, circa 1930s; 13-verso (Box 1610)
  - Alois Lang, the Christus of the Play, in His Studio, Oberammergau, Germany., circa 1930s; 14 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Alois Lang, the Christus of the Play, in His Studio, Oberammergau, Germany: The visitor at once notices the men without exception have, circa 1930s; 14-verso (Box 1610)
  - Jim Bausch (United States), Decathalon Victor, Established New World Records at the Olympic Games, Los Angeles., circa 1930s; 15 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Jim Bausch, the Decathalon Victor in Action. 1932 Olympics: Something of the magnitude of the program of the 1932 Olympic Games is, circa 1930s; 15-verso (Box 1610)
  - Floyd Gibbons, World Renowned War Correspondent and Adventurer at Large, "Speaking" at Chicago Conventions., circa 1930s; 16 (Box 1610)
  - Some Lindbergh Smiles from the Cockpit of a Lockheed Sirius Monoplane., circa 1930s; 17 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Some Lindbergh Smiles: It was on July 28, 1931, that Colonel and Mrs. Charles A. Lindbergh took off for the Orient at Washington, D.C., in, circa 1930s; 17-verso (Box 1610)
  - [untitled: Four men posing with golfing equipment and crowd], circa 1930s; 18 (Box 1610)
  - [untitled: Man putting while crowed looks on], circa 1930s; 19 (Box 1610)
  - Babe Ruth, King of Swat, at St. Petersburg, Florida., circa 1930s; 20 (Box 1610)
  - Jack Sharkey, Contestant for the World's Heavyweight Championship., circa 1930s; 21 (Box 1610)
  - Arthur Brisbane, Editorial Writer, Attended the Conventions at Chicago., circa 1930s; 22 (Box 1610)
  - Hon. Alfred E. Smith, Governor of New York and Democratic Candidate for President of the United States, 1928., circa 1930s; 23 (Box 1610)
  - Joffre and Pershing in Governor's Gardens, Paris, France., circa 1930s; 24 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Joffre and Pershing in Governor's Gardens, Paris, France: Joffre and Pershing! Here are two men who accepted responsibilities and made, circa 1930s; 24-verso (Box 1610)
  - Some of Our Two Million Fighters Ready for Home, Brest, France., circa 1930s; 25 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Some of Our Two Million Fighters Ready for Home, Brest: These hundreds of men in their slickers and web belts have passed through, circa 1930s; 25-verso (Box 1610)
  - "Back to Home Land!" Removing Casket of America's Unknown Soldier from the Olympia. Washington, D.C., circa 1930s; 26 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: America's Unknown Soldier Comes Home to his Native Soil: "The muffled drum's sad roll has beat The soldier's last tattoo; No more on, circa 1930s; 26-verso (Box 1610)
  - America's Most Notable Gathering of Military Heroes Left to Right, Jacques (Belgium), Diaz (Italy), Coolidge, Foch (France), Pershing, and Beatty (England), at His Right., circa 1930s; 27 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Military Heroes of World War at Kansas City: Rarely, indeed, has such a gathering of world famous men occurred at this assembled on, circa 1930s; 27-verso (Box 1610)
  - Clemenceau, Wilson, and Lloyd George Leaving Palace of Versailles After Signing Peace Treaty., circa 1930s; 28 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Leaving Palace of Versailles: Here we have the privilege of meeting face to face three of the most distinguished men of the age, three, circa 1930s; 28-verso (Box 1610)
  - [untitled image: Grand Canyon], circa 1930s; 29 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Without Third Dimension Effect: When viewed through the Telebinocular these two pictures appear as one, but no true depth or perspective, circa 1930s; 29-verso (Box 1610)
  - [untitled image: Grand Canyon], circa 1930s; 30 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Grand Canyon of the Yellowstone, Yellowstone Nat. Park: You are looking about southwest from a projecting angle in the rim of the canyon, circa 1930s; 30-verso (Box 1610)
  - [untitled image: Picking Lemons near Palermo], circa 1930s; 31 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Without Third Dimension Effect: When viewed through the Telebinocular these two pictures appear as one, but no true depth or perspective, circa 1930s; 31-verso (Box 1610)
  - [untitled image: Picking Lemons near Palermo], circa 1930s; 32 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Picking Lemons near Palermo: We are about two miles west of Palermo between the city and Monreale. All around us are similar fruit, circa 1930s; 32-verso (Box 1610)
  - [untitled image: Eccentric Growth of Cocoa Pod, Dominica, B. W. L.], circa 1930s; 33 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Without Third Dimension Effect: When viewed through the Telebinocular these two pictures appear as one, but no true depth or perspective, circa 1930s; 33-verso (Box 1610)
  - [untitled image: Eccentric Growth of Cocoa Pod, Dominica, B. W. L.], circa 1930s; 34 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Eccentric Growth of Cocoa Pod, Dominica, B. W. L.: The cacao tree is a native of America and it was Christopher Columubs who first, circa 1930s; 34-verso (Box 1610)
  - The Starting of the Second Heat in the 1,500-Meter Free-style Swimming Race, Olympic Games, Los Angeles., circa 1930s; 35 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: The Second Heat of the 1,500-Meter Free-Style Swimming Race, Los Angeles Olympics: Here we see the starting of the second heat of, circa 1930s; 35-verso (Box 1610)
  - Foreign Volunteer Corps (Scottish Section) Occupying First Defense Line between Chinese Territory (Chapel) and International Settlement, Shanghai., circa 1930s; 36 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: Foreign Volunteers of the Scottish Section: To understand the conditions at Shanghai, one must know something of its geography. It is, circa 1930s; 36-verso (Box 1610)
  - A Scene During thr 3000-Meter Steeplechase, Olympic Games, Los Angeles, Calif., circa 1930s; 37 (Box 1610)
  - Verso: The 3000 Meter Steeplechase, Los Angeles Olympics: "We swear that we will take part in the Olympic Games in loyal competition, respecting, circa 1930s; 37-verso (Box 1610)